<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Adam and Kelli Moser]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Adam and Kelli Moser]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/mosersinministry/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 20:38:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/mosersinministry/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adam & Kelli Moser | Joyfully Serving Jesus]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Adam & Kelli Moser | Joyfully Serving Jesus</h1><p>Disciple | Restore | Equip | Transform</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/eb7c4efd-b6cb-4069-8b9d-ffd1fc94989a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.mosersinministry.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b6b852d7-c1d9-44e6-9574-490cc7b6afac</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 20:38:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Us</h1><p>Adam and Kelli met at a prayer meeting in 2009 in Illinois. They got to know each other over a few years, and their friendship developed into a relationship. Adam moved to Kansas City in 2010 and they dated long distance. After several months Kelli moved in with some girls in the Kansas City area as their relationship developed. Adam began serving with Plumbline Ministries in August of 2011. On October 17, 2012 Adam asked Kelli to be his wife at the fountains in the plaza district of Kansas City. They were married in June of 2013 and began serving together in full-time ministry with Plumbline Ministries. In 2016 they gave birth to a daughter, Sophia. Adam's Bio:Adam helps with the communications and messaging of Plumbline. He also oversees the discipleship and missions divisions of the ministry. His desire is to see people fully in love with God and fulfilling their destinies on the earth.Kelli's Bio:Kelli is helping coordinate and organize Plumbline’s short-term missions program and daily administration for the ministry. She ministers alongside Adam as they teach, preach, and train the body of Christ in the fullness of the Lord. Kelli has a passion to know Christ intimately and to see the Word of God come alive and integrated into everyday life.To read our more recent updates, please visit the blog section of the website here.You can email us at:Adam@plumblinem.comKeljo@plumblinem.com</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.mosersinministry.com/about-us.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7357ab62-332e-448e-aa69-b27f51d736e6</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 20:38:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Give]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Give</h1><p>We have 70% of our monthly budget pledged, and we are needing to raise an additional $1000 per month. Those that partner with us in prayer and finances become part of our team. If we had 10 people join us at $100 a month we would be fully financially supported as a couple. No gift is too small, and we are thankful for every donation that we have received. We are over halfway through 2016 and we are hoping to grow our team, which is not just the Plumbline staff, but includes every person that is partnering with us in prayer and finances. If you sense that would like to join our partnership team through prayer or finances, please let us know. Tax-deductible contributions can be made through Plumbline Ministries in multiple ways to help us advance God’s Kingdom. Give Here </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.mosersinministry.com/give.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">87a8c6e2-bb3c-4473-a6cb-986b3b2a0e18</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 20:38:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>