<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Adam and Kelli Moser]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Adam and Kelli Moser]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/mosersinministry/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 23:07:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/mosersinministry/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International Trips]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>International Trips</h1><h2>8.22.13We have made it safely to Nairobi, Kenya. All team members and luggage arrived smoothly, except the obligatory concern when one member's boarding pass was not being granted in Brussels. After multiple help desks and showing paperwork, she was able to board and the last one to enter the plane. We did not experience any issues in customs, so all of the Bibles, books, supplies and hundreds of eyeglasses were able to go through without any issues. The fire at the Nairobi airport two weeks ago has shifted the international terminal to the domestic side, and everything was set up in tents.Last night we stayed at the Seventh Day Adventist guest house last night, and we had a vegetarian breakfast this morning that was good.We are on our way to exchange our US dollars for Kenyan shillings. Our team is going to shop for souvenirs, then we have a 7 hour drive, which passes the Great River Rift Valley to our meeting in Ndhiwa tonight.Our team spent time praying this morning and we are excited about what we sense The Lord is wanting to do.Testimonies:Friday August 23rdMorning meetingBrian and Adam taught with the pastors, leaders and laypeople.- Kelli, Amber and Sherry all led the children and taught on the fruit of the Spirit, joy, David and Goliath, God's promises, the giving tree.He shared on the Lord's desire to heal and prayed for several people who were healed. One man had two canes and struggled to walk because he had been shot in the back. After praying for some time, he was completely pain free and walking a little easier.Adam taught on the biblical basis for healing, and then Jon and Leigh had words of knowledge of several things The Lord wanted to heal.Crusade meetingMary and Clark shared their testimonies of how The Lord had been faithful in revealing himself and how Gods love was available for all people.Brian shared about justification by faith.Our estimate is that around 85 people came to The Lord. The pastors met with those that gave their lives to Jesus and informed them of how they could start to walk with Jesus with the local churches.- Revival meetingJon, Leigh and Amber shared on the goodness of God, God as our keeper and His desire to heal.- The Lord gave words of knowledge for eyes, ears, pain in stomach, foot and ankle issues, dizziness, fear, broken relationships, anger towards God, mouth teeth and gums, kidney stones, elbow and for a broken heart.- We had a woman who was healed of deafness (she had very little hearing), almost complete blindness, severe acid reflux and severe walking disability. She was so excited for the healing The Lord gave her, and we have a video of her testimony to come.- We prayed for Eunice's sister who was having pain in her stomach, and she was not able to attend the meeting. The next day we found out that The Lord had healed her completely by the word of The Lord going forth.- Pastor Paul's right eye was healed.- We had 2 women who had relief and felt better from the mouth, teeth and gum pain from the word of knowledge.- 1 man received prayer because he could not move without pain because of kidney stones. He was completely healed.- 1 woman was healed completely of ulcer pain immediately.- 1 woman had pain in her feet, and she felt blood flowing from her legs to her feet. It went from her hip to thigh to knee to calf as it spread to her feet.- 1 woman had pain in heart from losing two children to miscarriage. We prayed for barrenness to be broken off of her.- Friday Healings Total: 10- Friday salvations total: 85Saturday, August 24th- Jon, Leigh, Brian and Mary all helped with the children. They taught the Lord's Prayer, colored with the children, sang songs and played with them.- We saw a woman named Lucy had ruptured blood vessels in her legs due to high blood pressure get healed- A woman named Susanna was healed of a spirit of grief because three of her children had died.- We distributed reading glasses and Bibles to the people that were in need.Crusade Meeting- Sherry and Kelli shared their testimonies how The Lord had shown His love to them and provided for them.- Adam shared about creation, the fall and redemption through Jesus.Around 65 adults and 30 kids gave their lives to Jesus.Revival Meeting- Clark and Mary shared about Jesus working through their lives. A woman was 8 months pregnant that had pain in her belly. The pain was gone immediately.- Saturday Healings Total: 3- Saturday salvations total: 95Sunday, August 25th- Eunice had polyps in her nose and she said was completely healed. She could tell immediately because her voice changed.Elijah gave his life to The Lord and confessed his sins in front of us. He said instead of organizing youth for Satan as a politician he was going to influence people for Jesus. That afternoon at the service he was helping all of us find chairs and was actively involved.- Brian gave a prophetic word to the entire church about being a lightning rod and the church would be a beacon of light in the area.- A woman was healed of asthma in the Sunday morning service.- Brian prayed for a woman who had been in an accident and could hardly walk. He commanded the pain to stop and he prayed for her pelvis to come back into alignment. She was completely pain free after the prayer.Open Air Meeting- Jon and Leigh gave the Gospel message at the open air meeting. They shared about the mercy of God, gave testimony of what The Lord had done in their lives.- Jon had a prophetic word that The Lord wanted to heal incurable diseases, He prayed for people at the meeting and any family members with incurable diseases would be healed, which was around 10 people.- We had around 85 people give their lives to The Lord, of which 40 had their names recorded with the pastors.- Leigh sensed that The Lord wanted her to pray for people that had been in chronic pain or illness in their emotions or body and were being tormented at the end of the meeting. She prayed for three women that came forward, and she commanded that they be set free in Jesus' name.- We have heard multiple fellowships that were meeting on their own are now going to be a part of the Bethel churches in Ndhiwa.- We traveled to the town of Kisii Sunday evening and we are staying in a catholic guest house, which like a cross between a hostel and a hotel.We have been blessed with great team dynamics, good health and we are looking forward to what The Lord is going to do at the Kisii conference in the days to come.- Sunday Healings Total: 3- Sunday salvations total: 85- Monday, August 26th- Our team had a day of rest and we were able to go out in the town of Kisii. We walked through the streets and the markets, and some were able to update our blog posts at an Internet cafe.- In the afternoon many people were able to catch up on sleep and relax for a while.- We spent time talking about what The Lord is showing us and how we are doing individually. Some of our team was wrestling through how to process all that the Lord has been doing. - Tuesday, August 27thOur team visited two churches in the bush. The first church is called Otange is outside of Ndhiwa, and there were around 15-20 people ready for us when we arrived. The local pastors from the area also joined us. They have had so much rain that the shelter they were using to meet was washed away. They had constructed a rectangular shelter with straight limbs and white tarps for a roof.Ngope was the second village, and they met underneath a sycamore tree, which is what the name means. There were around 20 people that met as a church, and their were chairs and benches set up when we had gotten there.- Both churches were so thankful to have us visit them and to pray for The Lord to provide buildings for them to be able to meet when the rain and the sun were too intense.Wednesday, August 28th- We traveled to Oaru market area and began ministering at Bethel Worship Centre Church. When we arrived in the vicinity, they welcomed with a motorcycle escort while one of the passengers carried a poster of the conference.Morning Session- Mary ministered on blessing the name of The Lord before she had to leave for the States.- Brian shared on the Kingdom of God and how God's Kingdom advances.- Jon and Leigh shared on forgiveness and how The Lord says that we must forgive to be forgiven.- Words of Knowledge: headache, breathing issues or difficulty in breathing, female infertility, anger, envy, unforgiveness, upset stomach, upper bone in leg pain, confusion in thoughts,- 1 woman delivered of demonic spirit that was choking her every time she sang worship songs- 1 woman with stomach issues and leg pain healed- 1 woman with leg and bone pain healed- 1 woman healed from unforgiveness, anger and pain in her legs from the unforgiveness.-1 woman with heart issues felt much better--we believed from a word of wisdom that she had blood pressure issues- 1 woman with breathing or asthma issues healed, Joshua's spiritual father healed from pain in knees and legs had swollen and inflammation issues healed- 1 man had pain and arthritis in his hand healed- 1 woman had confusion and pain her legs and breathing issues felt something lifted off of her and her breathing was better- 1 woman with breathing issues healed- 1 woman with rib, knee, and feet pain and she was healed from her knees and rib and her feet were better but not healed completely- 1 woman with pain her leg and another with a bad cough and breathing issues prayed for but unclear if she was totally healed- 2-3 men with stomach issues and back issues and hip pain all healed- 1 woman had leg and body pain healedOpen Air Meeting- Adam and Kelli shared testimonies, and Amber preached the Gospel message. 11 people came to know The Lord.Revival Meeting- The group was primarily comprised of young people with a few adults. Adam preached on being a disciple and Kelli shared about not being put down because they are young.- One young adult man came forward to give his life to Christ.-Wednesday Total Salvations: 12- Wednesday Total Healings: 14-15Thursday, August 29th- On our way to the meeting we were stopped by the police and they said that our stickers didn't match on the van. They wanted us to go the police station, but then they showed us favor.- A few minutes later some of our team saw a motorcycle going fast down a hill, and he lost control. We stopped to care for the man and pray for him. He had a gash on the left side of his head, on both hands, his wrist looked injured and his collarbone was broken. Our first aid kit was useful to clean the wound and we prayed for the bone to be set and the pain to diminish.- The local pastors held the first session before we arrived, and then Brian preached on the advancing Kingdom of God and the rhythm of the Kingdom. He also taught on the authority we have in prayer.- Sherry taught on how to be aware of the enemy's schemes in our lives and around us. Amber followed up with teaching on how God is our keeper. - the words of knowledge were: breathing problems, problems with blood issues, throat problems, skin infections, head injury, eye problems, kidney pain and urinary tract problems or infections, ear pain or deafness, hip pain, jaw or teeth pain- 4 people with sore throat healed- 1 woman neck stiffness and couldn't turn her neck completely healed, and blindness healed.- George had an itchy ear and an eye issue. His ear was healed and eye was starting to feel better.- 1 boy healed of deafness- 1 girl healed of deafness- 1 woman pain in knees healed- 1 woman pain in hips much better but still had some pain- 1 man with high blood pressure and The Lord gave a word that The Lord wanted to heal both his high blood pressure and that his arm would grow out from the elbow down.- 2 women with pain in and we found a spirit of infirmity that kept moving around all over, both were healed of the demonic afflicting tormenting spirits.- 1 man with a throat issue that was healed- 2 men had eye issues - one was day light blindness and they were both healed. He even went outside and tested it and said it was good!- 1 man got a word of knowledge that The Lord was going to restore the relationship with his daughter. - 1 man had high blood pressure that had been acting up and he felt completely better. Their was also a word that the man would have resources to help him and others.- 1 woman healed of deafness/hearing loss and The Lord showed that she also had a pain in her chest that went from her chest and all the way down her admen and around her back and she was healed of all of it.- 1 woman had abdominal pain and pain that was completely healed- 1 girl had pain in her knees and legs plus the teeth that were all healed- 1 woman with a heart issue was healed and had hip pain that will be tested tonight when she usually gets her pain.- 1 man had breathing issue and eye sight healed- 3 men and 4 women with pain in the skin every morning were prayed for and we will see tomorrow if they were healed.- 1 woman with pain in shoulder and kidney was completely healed- 1 boy had pain in his teeth while eating and when the weather was cold was prayed for and he will tell us tomorrow if it is better.Open Air Meeting- Sherry shared a testimony about how Jesus had made a difference in her life and had always provided.- Brian shared the message of Jesus, and there were around 130 people that came to The Lord. He also prayed for anyone that had sickness, although there is not a record of how many people were healed.- The dancers invited Adam, Kelli and Sherry to dance for a few songs. The people loved it, and they laughed many times. It was a great time had by all, and the pictures and videos are proof. There was a rainbow in the sky after we finished :)Revival MeetingClark shared about the woman at the well and Kathy shared about pouring out our problems to God, Him pouring in His Spirit, and we pour forth our lives to others.Thursday Total Healings: 28Thursday Total Salvations: 130Friday, August 30th- Clark shared on the normal Christian birth and how God wants to work in every Christian's life. Kathy shared about her testimony about how the love of God brought forgiveness and healing to her life. Adam shared about biblical finances and how to steward what The Lord brings our way. Kelli shared that The Lord wanted the pastors, leaders and church-people to bless one another and pray for each other. Everyone got in groups of three to four and prayed together. It was a powerful time of unifying the body of Christ.- Adam invited the presence of The Lord to heal for the entire group and had them pray for each other and everyone that needed healing that was in the meeting.- One of the men with skin allergies was completely healed after our prayers yesterday.- One woman was healed of all the pain in her body.- We had testimonies of how many lives were touched and affected by The Lord, by the teachings, and by the team.- One man gave thanks for the coming together of the multiple churches and denominations. - After they had prayed for one another, and there were 13 partial healings and 8 complete healings.- Jon, Leigh, Sherry, Brian and Amber worked with the children and ministered to them.- The team set up the reading glasses in stations so that people could test them out and get the correct strength.- We distributed the Bibles, books and training materials through Pastor Joshua to the pastors, leaders and churches that were in need. We gave away 10 Kisii Bibles, around 20 English Bibles and dozens of books. The other Bibles were purchased were ordered in Kisii Town.Crusade MeetingAdam and Kelli gave the Gospel message together, and then made an appeal for people to come to know Jesus. There were approximately 430 people that made decisions to follow Jesus, and we had the opportunity as a team to talk to a good portion of them as a group after the meeting. We encouraged them to pray, fellowshipping with other believers and start being affected by the Bible or reading the Bible if they had access to it.We journeyed to the home that Pastor Joshua and George grew up with their family and saw the church and orphanage on the land. It was perched up on top of a hill, and the family farm went all the way down to the river at the bottom of the valley. There are around 30 boys that lived at orphanage, and there were a few people that helped watch after them.Revival Meeting:- Amber shared about slowing down and taking a rest and a selah.- Jon and Leigh shared on being healed of shame, guilt and rejection, and there was a time of praying for those effects to be broken off of people's lives.Total Friday Healings: 20Total Friday Salvations: 430Saturday, August 31st- Brian, Jon and Leigh shared on the faithfulness of God, loving others well and biblical meditation.- They had 6 words of knowledge and several individual prophetic words and one corporate prophetic word. We didn't get an estimate of how many people The Lord touched.- Adam, Kelli, Kathy and Sherry worked with over 100 children. They split them into two groups and had a lot of time interacting and playing with them.- We gave out right about 125 Crusade Meeting- Jon and Leigh shared the Gospel message and about how The Lord wanted to minister to very specific needs as well. We saw 257 come to Lord, most in the group meeting and led some individually after the meeting as well.- Jon had a word of knowledge for foot injuries.- One boy was healed of his foot injury and open sore.- One man was healed of pain from his broken arm as well as pain in his chest and back. He had a huge smile afterwards and told us that the pain was all gone.- One woman had us pray for her four year old girl because it had been lame since birth. She then wanted to accept Jesus as savior.- We prayed for a young lady named Eunice that was born with cerebral palsy that had lameness in her left hand that was closed and her left foot was turned. She was able to open her left hand for the first time and her leg started to turn and straighten so she did not have to walk on the complete outside of her foot anymore.- There was a man that was dancing in the crowd almost every day that came forward to receive Jesus. He told us that he had demons and that he wanted prayer. He was healed of sores in his mouth earlier in the service. We also prayed that the grip that alcohol had had in his life would be broken.- Onyiengo had been around the house and the meetings all week. He rarely spoke and would come and take food from our table. His brother has club feet and we were told their parents are first cousins and involved in witchcraft. He sat down after dinner with part of the team and did not want to receive prayer. Leigh handed him cookies, and then he received prayer and came to Jesus. - Total Saturday Salvations: 258- Total Saturday Healings: 4Sunday, September 1st- Asante Yesu kwa kuwa wewe u mwema. We thank you Jesus because you are so good.Testimonies - We had a man come forward and said that his headaches and pain in his back was completely gone after he was prayed for earlier in the week.- One woman came forward because The Lord healed her legs and her head pain.- A man named George was prayed for earlier in the week because of leg pain, and now he can kick, jump and move easily.- Pastor Peter gave testimony that his blood pressure had gone down.- One woman came forward because her legs were healed this week.- Brian shared the morning message on biblical faith and how The Lord wants to awaken our lives in all of the areas of faith.- He prayed for different people corporately that needed healing through words of knowledge that he and the team received.- There were 3 people healed completely and 2 partial healings. We got testimony of another healing that happened a few days earlier.- Total Sunday Healings: 6Total Healings: 88Total Ndhiwa Salvations: 265Total Kisii Salvations: 830Our estimate is that 1000 people came to Lord throughout the meetings (because children may have raised their hands more than once.)</h2><p>Kenya August 2015 TripJambo! That is a true Swahili hello. What a full month August was for us. We are so very thankful for all of your prayers and support as we prepared for and ministered in Kenya.We started our 14 day journey with our five person team by traveling a little over 25 hours to get to Kenya. The Lord gave grace for all of us as we journeyed and tried to adjust to our new time zone. When we landed in Nairobi we were able to have a night of rest at our hotel and enjoy stretching our legs!The conferences were held western Kenya in an area close to Kisii called Marani and south Central Kenya in Githurai, which is just east of the capital city of Nairobi. We ministered to approximately 100 leaders and pastors between the two cities. There were several denominations and backgrounds that organized and attended the meetings. We gave out certificates of completion to all of the participants that were trained in the seminars. We saw the Lord move powerfully with several healings and strengthened the attendees through the teachings. Here are a few testimonies from the trip:Marani - One woman had been to doctors for problem with her leg that was not moving well with numbness after a stroke. She had pain in her body and breathing problems/asthma. She is able to move her leg regularly and able to breathe normally.- 1 young man had issues breathing. He felt heaviness lift off of his chest and he could breathe easier.At the open air service, we probably had 4000-5000.There were around 200 adults and 300 children that raised their hands and gave their lives to the Lord.Saturday, August 22ndWe taught again in Marani. The teachings were studying the Bible, biblical meditation, prayer and unity.One woman had diabetes, weakness in her legs, and very little movement in her right arm. The Lord allowed her to be able to stretch out her hand. She was able to stand more easily and she felt blood flowing through her legs and no more pain in her knees.We prayed for a woman who had a cyst on the top of her wrist. The pain went away and she said she thought she would be able to cancel her surgery that was scheduled. It was no longer tight, reduced in size two times and was able to move around more freely. It was rock hard before and she said it felt like it broke away and became soft.- The Kenyans thought there were between 10-15k people. We had over 1300 people respond to follow Jesus at the meeting.There was a woman that had stomach issues, back pain and leg pain. She came forward for prayer and said she felt better in all of those areas.- Over 20,000 people approximately attended the Marani crusade to hear about Jesus, and approximately 1400-1500 gave their lives to the Lord.Our teachings were on healing, how to study the Bible, biblical finances, unity, discipleship, destiny and more. In both locations we held evangelistic crusades daily where we preached the Gospel and lead people to salvation. We saw around 3,500 people make decisions for Christ and connect to local churches, and there were also 27 documented healings. We will be posting many more pictures on our website and Facebook soon. Your prayers and financial partnership are changing lives for eternity around the world, and may the Lord pour out His blessings upon you richly!We are so blessed to be doing what the Lord has called us to both here and around the world. Thank you for believing in us and joining in the adventure of advancing the Kingdom!</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7d8a5486-f1c5-4496-88e8-490695b64111.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.mosersinministry.com/kenya-trips.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">84aad65a-4aa5-4187-89da-9d88f7a1c72a</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 23:07:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adam & Kelli Moser | Joyfully Serving Jesus]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Adam & Kelli Moser | Joyfully Serving Jesus</h1><p>Disciple | Restore | Equip | Transform</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/eb7c4efd-b6cb-4069-8b9d-ffd1fc94989a.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.mosersinministry.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b6b852d7-c1d9-44e6-9574-490cc7b6afac</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 23:06:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Us</h1><p>Adam and Kelli met at a prayer meeting in 2009 in Illinois. They got to know each other over a few years, and their friendship developed into a relationship. Adam moved to Kansas City in 2010 and they dated long distance. After several months Kelli moved in with some girls in the Kansas City area as their relationship developed. Adam began serving with Plumbline Ministries in August of 2011. On October 17, 2012 Adam asked Kelli to be his wife at the fountains in the plaza district of Kansas City. They were married in June of 2013 and began serving together in full-time ministry with Plumbline Ministries. In 2016 they gave birth to a daughter, Sophia. Adam's Bio:Adam helps with the communications and messaging of Plumbline. He also oversees the discipleship and missions divisions of the ministry. His desire is to see people fully in love with God and fulfilling their destinies on the earth.Kelli's Bio:Kelli is helping coordinate and organize Plumbline’s short-term missions program and daily administration for the ministry. She ministers alongside Adam as they teach, preach, and train the body of Christ in the fullness of the Lord. Kelli has a passion to know Christ intimately and to see the Word of God come alive and integrated into everyday life.To read our more recent updates, please visit the blog section of the website here.You can email us at:Adam@plumblinem.comKeljo@plumblinem.com</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.mosersinministry.com/about-us.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7357ab62-332e-448e-aa69-b27f51d736e6</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 23:07:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Give]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Give</h1><p>We have 70% of our monthly budget pledged, and we are needing to raise an additional $1000 per month. Those that partner with us in prayer and finances become part of our team. If we had 10 people join us at $100 a month we would be fully financially supported as a couple. No gift is too small, and we are thankful for every donation that we have received. We are over halfway through 2016 and we are hoping to grow our team, which is not just the Plumbline staff, but includes every person that is partnering with us in prayer and finances. If you sense that would like to join our partnership team through prayer or finances, please let us know. Tax-deductible contributions can be made through Plumbline Ministries in multiple ways to help us advance God’s Kingdom. Give Here </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.mosersinministry.com/give.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">87a8c6e2-bb3c-4473-a6cb-986b3b2a0e18</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2016 23:06:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>